What if you wished everyone - and everything - would just go away!
Nothing is a comedy, fantasy, science fiction film directed by Vincenzo Natali.
The film tells the story of two good friends who live together, Andrew, an agoraphobic travel agent who works
from his home, and Dave, a loser who works in an office where he is treated with contempt.
Just when it seems things can't get any worse for the two, the entire world outside
of their house disappears and is replaced with an endless white void.
Dave, played by David Hewlett.
Andrew, played by Andrew Miller.
Man In Suit, played by Gordon Pinsent.
Sara, played by Marie-Josée Croze.
Crawford, played by Andrew Lowery.
Little Girl, played by Elana Shilling.
Nothing is a 2003 Canadian surrealist comedy-drama
film directed by Vincenzo Natali.
It stars David Hewlett and Andrew Miller.
The film explores themes of loser, bullying, leere, best friend, cowardliness.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.